<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<!--Abilities-->
	<string name="jack_marshal_name">\'Jack Marshal</string>
	<string name="jack_marshal_longDesc">This character is skilled at instructing steamjacks to act.  The \'jack marshal must know the cortex\'s native language to instrcut it as well as the \'jack\'s cortex lock codes. Bonded steamjacks cannot be affected by this ability.</string>
	<string name="jack_marshal_shortDesc">Can control \'jacks</string>
	<string name="jack_marshal_page">157</string>

	<string name="ace_commander_name">Ace Commander</string>
	<string name="ace_commander_longDesc">The character gains an extra quick action during each of their turns that can only be used to drive a \'jack</string>
	<string name="ace_commander_shortDesc">Extra quick action for \'jack drive</string>
	<string name="ace_commander_page">157</string>

	<string name="acrobatics_name">Acrobatics</string>
	<string name="acrobatics_longDesc">The character can advance through other characters if they have enough movement to move completely past the other characters\' bases.  The character also gains +3 on Jumping skill rolls.</string>
	<string name="acrobatics_shortDesc">Can move through others; +3 Jumping</string>
	<string name="acrobatics_page">157</string>

	<string name="advisor_name">Advisor</string>
	<string name="advisor_longDesc">While B2B with this character, friendly characters gain +1 to their command range.</string>
	<string name="advisor_shortDesc">B2B friends get +1 CMD</string>
	<string name="advisor_page">157</string>

	<string name="ambush_name">Ambush</string>
	<string name="ambush_longDesc">During the first round of an encounter, this character gains boosted attack and damage rolls against enemies that have not yet activated</string>
	<string name="ambush_shortDesc">Boosted rolls against flat-footed enemies</string>
	<string name="ambush_page">157</string>

	<string name="anatomical_precision_name">Anatomical Precision</string>
	<string name="anatomical_precision_longDesc">When this character hits a living target with a melee attack but the damage roll fails to exceed the target\'s ARM, the target suffers d3 damage points instead of the damage rolled.</string>
	<string name="anatomical_precision_shortDesc">If no melee damage, d3 damage</string>
	<string name="anatomical_precision_page">157</string>

	<string name="appraise_name">Appraise</string>
	<string name="appraise_longDesc">This character can judge the value of most fine goods with an inspection.  Truly good fakes might require a Detection + INT roll to spot.</string>
	<string name="appraise_shortDesc">Can value goods at a glance</string>
	<string name="appraise_page">157</string>

	<string name="arcane_assassin_name">Arcane Assassin</string>
	<string name="arcane_assassin_longDesc">When making attacks, this character ignores focus points overboosting the target\'s Power Field and spell effects adding to its ARM or DEF.</string>
	<string name="arcane_assassin_shortDesc">Ignore DEF and ARM boosting spells</string>
	<string name="arcane_assassin_page">157</string>

	<string name="arcane_defenses_name">Arcane Defenses</string>
	<string name="arcane_defenses_longDesc">This character gains +3 ARM against magic attacks</string>
	<string name="arcane_defenses_shortDesc">+3 ARM against magic</string>
	<string name="arcane_defenses_page">157</string>

	<string name="arcane_engineer_name">Arcane Engineer</string>
	<string name="arcane_engineer_longDesc">This character can reroll failed Mechanikal Engineering rolls.  Each failed roll can be rerolled only once as a result of Arcane Engineer.</string>
	<string name="arcane_engineer_shortDesc">Can reroll Mech. Engineering rolls</string>
	<string name="arcane_engineer_page">157</string>

	<string name="arcane_precision_name">Arcane Precision</string>
	<string name="arcane_precision_longDesc">When this character forfeits their movement to aim with a ranged weapon, they ignore stealth that turn.</string>
	<string name="arcane_precision_shortDesc">Ignore stealth when aiming</string>
	<string name="arcane_precision_page">157</string>

	<string name="arcane_scholar_name">Arcane Scholar</string>
	<string name="arcane_scholar_longDesc">This character can have a number of spells equal to INTx3, rather than INTx2</string>
	<string name="arcane_scholar_shortDesc">Can know INTx3 spells</string>
	<string name="arcane_scholar_page">157</string>

	<string name="astute_name">Astute</string>
	<string name="astute_longDesc">This character can reroll failed Detection rols.  Each failed roll can be rerolled only once as a result of Astute.</string>
	<string name="astute_shortDesc">Can reroll Detection rolls</string>
	<string name="astute_page">157</string>

	<string name="backstab_name">Backstab</string>
	<string name="backstab_longDesc">This character gains an additional die on their back strike damage rolls.</string>
	<string name="backstab_shortDesc">+1 damage die on back strikes</string>
	<string name="backstab_page">157</string>

	<string name="battle_commander_name">Battle Commander</string>
	<string name="battle_commander_longDesc">This character can use one battle plan during each turn without spending a feat point.</string>
	<string name="battle_commander_shortDesc">One free battle plan/turn</string>
	<string name="battle_commander_page">157</string>

	<string name="battle_plan_call_to_action_name">Battle Plan: Call To Action</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_call_to_action_longDesc">The character can spend one feat point to use this ability.  Using a battle plan is a quick action.  When a character uses this battle plan, each friendly character in this character\'s command range who is under their command and is knocked down immediately stands up or goes prone.</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_call_to_action_shortDesc">Feat: Knocked-down allies stand up</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_call_to_action_page">157</string>

	<string name="battle_plan_coordinated_strike_name">Battle Plan: Coordinated Strike</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_coordinated_strike_longDesc">The character can spend one feat point to use this ability during a surprise round.  Using a battle plan is a quick action.  When a character uses this battle plan, each friendly character in this character\'s command range can immediately make one attack.  After these attacks, the surprise round ends and the characters are detected.</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_coordinated_strike_shortDesc">Feat: Attack as one in surprise round</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_coordinated_strike_page">157</string>

	<string name="battle_plan_desperate_pace_name">Battle Plan: Desparate Pace</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_desperate_pace_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point to use this ability.  Using a battle plan is a quick action.  When a character uses this battle plan, friendly characters gain +2\" movement for the round.</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_desperate_pace_shortDesc">Feat: Allies get +2\" move</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_desperate_pace_page">158</string>

	<string name="battle_plan_go_to_ground_name">Battle Plan: Go To Ground</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_go_to_ground_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point to use this ability.  Using a battle plan is a quick action.  When a character uses this battle plan, each friendly character gains cover, does not suffer blast damage, and does not block LOS until they move, are placed, or are engaged.</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_go_to_ground_shortDesc">Feat: Allies dig in</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_go_to_ground_page">158</string>

	<string name="battle_plan_reconnaissance_name">Battle Plan: Reconnaissance</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_reconnaissance_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point to use this ability.  Using a battle plan is a quick action.  When a character uses this battle plan, the character and friendly characters in this command range gain Pathfinder for one round.</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_reconnaissance_shortDesc">Feat: Allies get Pathfinder</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_reconnaissance_page">158</string>

	<string name="battle_plan_shadow_name">Battle Plan: Shadow</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_shadow_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point to use this ability.  Using a battle plan is a quick action.  When a character uses this battle plan, each friendly character gains Prowl (p.165) for one round.</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_shadow_shortDesc">Feat: Allies get Prowl</string>
	<string name="battle_plan_shadow_page">158</string>

	<string name="bayonet_charge_name">Bayonet Charge</string>
	<string name="bayonet_charge_longDesc">When this character charges with a ranged weapon that has a bayonet, after moving but before making the charge attack, they can make one ranged attack targeting the charge target (unless already in melee with the target at turn start).  When resolving the ranged attack, the target-in-melee attack roll penalty does not apply.  If the target is not in melee range after movement, the charater may make the ranged attack before their turn ends.  The charge attack for a Bayonet Charge must be made with a bayonet.</string>
	<string name="bayonet_charge_shortDesc">Extra ranged attack on charge w/ bayonet</string>
	<string name="bayonet_charge_page">158</string>

	<string name="big_game_hunter_name">Big Game Hunter</string>
	<string name="big_game_hunter_longDesc">When a character with Big Game Hunter makes a melee or ranged attack against a natural animal or beast native to the wilds of Immoren, they gain a bonus on attack rolls equal to their Survival skill.</string>
	<string name="big_game_hunter_shortDesc">+Survival to attack rolls on beasts</string>
	<string name="big_game_hunter_page">158</string>

	<string name="binding_name">Binding</string>
	<string name="binding_longDesc">When a character ties up, manacles, or otherwise restrains another character, add +3 to the skill roll difficulty for the bound character to escape.</string>
	<string name="binding_shortDesc">+3 to escape your bindings</string>
	<string name="binding_page">158</string>

	<string name="blaster_name">Blaster</string>
	<string name="blaster_longDesc">This character gains +2 to hit with electrical ranged attacks</string>
	<string name="blaster_shortDesc">+2 to electric ranged attacks</string>
	<string name="blaster_page">158</string>

	<string name="blood_spiller_name">Blood Spiller</string>
	<string name="blood_spiller_longDesc">The character gains +2 on damage rolls against living characters</string>
	<string name="blood_spiller_shortDesc">+2 damage against living</string>
	<string name="blood_spiller_page">158</string>

	<string name="bodge_name">Bodge</string>
	<string name="bodge_longDesc">The character can make temporary repairs to a steamjack in combat.  Bodging is a full action.  The mechanik makes an INT+Mechanikal Engineering roll against target number 14.  If the roll suceeds, the steamjack regains 1 damage box in each of its crippled systems.  If the roll fails, the character may try again next round.</string>
	<string name="bodge_shortDesc">Repair crippled \'jack systems (14)</string>
	<string name="bodge_page">319</string>

	<string name="bodyguard_name">Bodyguard</string>
	<string name="bodyguard_longDesc">This character is not limited in the number of times they can use Shield Guard each round.</string>
	<string name="bodyguard_shortDesc">Unlimited Shield Guards</string>
	<string name="bodyguard_page">158</string>

	<string name="bomber_name">Bomber</string>
	<string name="bomber_longDesc">When this character\'s grenade ranged attack deviates, you may reroll the direction and/or distance of deviation.  A roll can only be rerolled once as a result of Bomber.</string>
	<string name="bomber_shortDesc">May reroll grenade deviations</string>
	<string name="bomber_page">158</string>

	<string name="bond_name">Bond</string>
	<string name="bond_longDesc">This ability may be taken more than once.  Each time a character takes this ability they gain a bonding slot that can be bonded with a steamjack to make it part of their battlegroup, warcaster armor to gain the benefits of the power field and overboosting, or a mechanika weapon to spend focus points to boost attack and damage rolls and make additional attacks with it.  To form a bond, a character must spend a full action touching the object they intend to bond to.  Forming a bond with a steamjack requires the warcaster to know its cortex\'s native language and the pass codes to any locks on its cortex.  A character can break a bond at will and recover the used slot.  A character cannot bond with an object bonded to another character.  Bonded steamjacks are not affected by marshalling.</string>
	<string name="bond_shortDesc">Bond with Mechanika</string>
	<string name="bond_page">158</string>

	<string name="brew_master_name">Brew Master</string>
	<string name="brew_master_longDesc">This character can reroll failed Alchemy rolls.  Each failed roll can only be rerolled once from Brew Master.</string>
	<string name="brew_master_shortDesc">Reroll Alchemy rolls</string>
	<string name="brew_master_page">159</string>

	<string name="camouflage_name">Camouflage</string>
	<string name="camouflage_longDesc">This character gains an additional +2 DEF when benefitting from concealment or cover.</string>
	<string name="camouflage_shortDesc">+2 DEF when concealed</string>
	<string name="camouflage_page">159</string>

	<string name="card_sharp_name">Card Sharp</string>
	<string name="card_sharp_longDesc">This character can cheat.  When a character uses this ability, they add an extra die to Gambling skill rolls and drop the lowest result.  Anyone watching the character play can make a Detection skill roll to catch the cheater.  The skill roll target number is equal to the cheater\'s INT + AGL + Gambling skill.</string>
	<string name="card_sharp_shortDesc">Cheat when gambling</string>
	<string name="card_sharp_page">159</string>

	<string name="cautious_advance_name">Cautious Advance</string>
	<string name="cautious_advance_longDesc">This character gains one extra quick action each turn that can be used only to take cover.</string>
	<string name="cautious_advance_shortDesc">Free quick action to take cover</string>
	<string name="cautious_advance_page">159</string>

	<string name="cavalry_charge_name">Cavalry Charge</string>
	<string name="cavalry_charge_longDesc">This character can make a cavalry charge (p. 214) while riding a mount designated as a warhorse.</string>
	<string name="cavalry_charge_shortDesc">Can make cavalry charges</string>
	<string name="cavalry_charge_page">159</string>

	<string name="chain_attack_bleed_out_name">Chain Attack: Bleed Out</string>
	<string name="chain_attack_bleed_out_longDesc">If this character fights with two melee hand weapons and hits the same living target with both initial attacks, after resolving the attacks they can immediately make one additional melee attack against the target.  If it hits, it does not inflict damage but the target must forfeit either its movement or action on its next Activation Phase.</string>
	<string name="chain_attack_bleed_out_shortDesc">Chain: forfeit move/action</string>
	<string name="chain_attack_bleed_out_page">159</string>

	<string name="chain_attack_pin_down_name">Chain Attack: Pin Down</string>
	<string name="chain_attack_pin_down_longDesc">If this character hits the same living target with initial attacks from two pistols, after resolving the attacks they can immediately make one additional ranged attack against the target, ignoring ROF.  If it hits, it does not inflict damage.  Instead, the target hit can advance up to 2\", and then it is knocked down.</string>
	<string name="chain_attack_pin_down_shortDesc">Chain: advance and knockdown</string>
	<string name="chain_attack_pin_down_page">159</string>

	<string name="choir_name">Choir</string>
	<string name="choir_longDesc">A character gains a cumulative +1 on magic attack rolls for each other friendly character of their faith with this ability within 1\" of them.</string>
	<string name="choir_shortDesc">+1 Magic attack rolls / Choir w/i 1\"</string>
	<string name="choir_page">159</string>

	<string name="cleave_name">Cleave</string>
	<string name="cleave_longDesc">When this character incapacitates one or more enemies with a melee attack made with a great weapon during his turn, the character can make one additional melee attack immediately after the attack is resolved.  A character can only gain one additional attack from Cleave each turn.</string>
	<string name="cleave_shortDesc">Extra attack each turn upon kill</string>
	<string name="cleave_page">159</string>

	<string name="combat_rider_name">Combat Rider</string>
	<string name="combat_rider_longDesc">While this character is riding a mount designated as a warhorse, the mount can make one impact attack against a target in its melee range if the mount and rider did not charge this turn.</string>
	<string name="combat_rider_shortDesc">Warhorse makes impact attacks</string>
	<string name="combat_rider_page">159</string>

	<string name="conniver_name">Conniver</string>
	<string name="conniver_longDesc">The character can reroll failed Bribery and Deception-based social skill rolls.  Each roll can be rerolled only once as a result of Conniver.</string>
	<string name="conniver_shortDesc">May reroll Bribery, Deception</string>
	<string name="conniver_page">159</string>

	<string name="cover_identity_name">Cover Identity</string>
	<string name="cover_identity_longDesc">The character has an established cover identity with its own history, contacts, and crimial record (or lack of one).  The character\'s Disguise rolls while using the cover identity are automatically boosted.  Choose a career for the cover identity.  The character gains one occupational skill at level 1 from the cover identity\'s career.  The cover identity must be reasonably believable.  This ability can be taken multiple times, each with a different cover identity.</string>
	<string name="cover_identity_shortDesc">Gain a cover identity</string>
	<string name="cover_identity_page">159</string>

	<string name="crackshot_name">Crackshot</string>
	<string name="crackshot_longDesc">When making a ranged or magic attack against a target with concealment, cover, or elevation, this character gains +2 on the attack roll.</string>
	<string name="crackshot_shortDesc">+2 to attack against conceal/cover/elevation</string>
	<string name="crackshot_page">159</string>

	<string name="craft_rune_shot_name">Craft Rune Shot</string>
	<string name="craft_rune_shot_longDesc">The character can craft run shot ammunition.  A character with this ability and a rune shot casting kit pays 1 gc for materials to make one round of rune shot ammo.  The character must inscribe the round by hand.  A character can craft up to five rune shot cartridges in an hour.</string>
	<string name="craft_rune_shot_shortDesc">Craft tune shot ammo</string>
	<string name="craft_rune_shot_page">160</string>

	<string name="crossbowman_name">Crossbowman</string>
	<string name="crossbowman_longDesc">The character can reload a crossbow as a quick action instead of a full action.</string>
	<string name="crossbowman_shortDesc">Reload crossbow as quick action</string>
	<string name="crossbowman_page">160</string>

	<string name="defender_name">Defender</string>
	<string name="defender_longDesc">Once per round, when a friendly character within this character\'s command range is hit with an enemy attack, immediately after the attack has been resolved this character can advance toward the enemy character, up to 2\", and make one melee attack.</string>
	<string name="defender_shortDesc">On friendly hit, move+attack</string>
	<string name="defender_page">160</string>

	<string name="defensive_line_name">Defensive Line</string>
	<string name="defensive_line_longDesc">While this character is B2B with one or more friendly characters, it gains +1 ARM.  If any of the friendly characters also have this ability, the bonus increases to +2 ARM</string>
	<string name="defensive_line_shortDesc">+1/+2 ARM while B2B w/ friendly</string>
	<string name="defensive_line_page">160</string>

	<string name="dig_in_name">Dig In</string>
	<string name="dig_in_longDesc">While they have a spade in hand, this character can make a quick action to dig a fox hole.  Until they move, are placed, go prone, or are engaged, the character gains cover, does not suffer blast damage, and does not block line of sight.  This ability cannot be used during a turn where the character ran.</string>
	<string name="dig_in_shortDesc">Cover, immune to blast, not block LOS</string>
	<string name="dig_in_page">160</string>

	<string name="disease_resistance_name">Disease Resistance</string>
	<string name="disease_resistance_longDesc">The character makes boosted rolls to resist disease and infection.</string>
	<string name="disease_resistance_shortDesc">Boosted rolls against disease</string>
	<string name="disease_resistance_page">160</string>

	<string name="dispel_name">Dispel</string>
	<string name="dispel_longDesc">When this character hits an enemy with a melee attack, they can spend 1 feat point to cause any upkeep spells on that enemy to expire immediately.</string>
	<string name="dispel_shortDesc">Feat: remove enemy upkeeps</string>
	<string name="dispel_page">160</string>

	<string name="dodger_name">Dodger</string>
	<string name="dodger_longDesc">When the character is missed by enemy attacks except during an advance, they can immediately advance up to 2\" after the attack is resolved.  They cannot be targeted by free strikes during the movement.</string>
	<string name="dodger_shortDesc">Move 2\" when missed</string>
	<string name="dodger_page">161</string>

	<string name="drive_ancillary_attack_name">Drive: Ancillary Attack</string>
	<string name="drive_ancillary_attack_longDesc">This ability uses a quick action.  A controlled steamjack immediately makes one normal melee or ranged attack.</string>
	<string name="drive_ancillary_attack_shortDesc">Drive: immediate attack</string>
	<string name="drive_ancillary_attack_page">161</string>

	<string name="drive_assault_name">Drive: Assault</string>
	<string name="drive_assault_longDesc">This ability uses a quick action.  The steamjack charges during its turn this round without spending focus or being forced.  As part of that charge, after moving but before making its charge attack, the steamjack can make one ranged attack targeting its charge target unless it was in melee with its charge target at the start of the turn.  When resolving the ranged attack, the steamjack does not suffer the target-in-melee penalty.  If the target is not in melee range after charge movement, the steamjack can make the ranged attack before its turn ends.</string>
	<string name="drive_assault_shortDesc">Drive: ranged attack on charge</string>
	<string name="drive_assault_page">161</string>

	<string name="drive_off_road_name">Drive: Off Road</string>
	<string name="drive_off_road_longDesc">This ability uses a quick action.  The steamjack gains the Pathfinder ability during its turn this round and must use its normal movement and combat action to charge or slam.</string>
	<string name="drive_off_road_shortDesc">Drive: Pathfinder on charge/slam</string>
	<string name="drive_off_road_page">161</string>

	<string name="drive_pronto_name">Drive: Pronto</string>
	<string name="drive_pronto_longDesc">This ability uses a quick action.  The steamjack makes a full advance.</string>
	<string name="drive_pronto_shortDesc">Drive: Full advance</string>
	<string name="drive_pronto_page">161</string>

	<string name="dual_shot_name">Dual Shot</string>
	<string name="dual_shot_longDesc">The character can forfeit their movement during their turn to make one additional ranged attack with a pistol or rifle.</string>
	<string name="dual_shot_shortDesc">Forfeit move for +1 ranged attack</string>
	<string name="dual_shot_page">161</string>

	<string name="elemental_mastery_name">Elemental Mastery</string>
	<string name="elemental_mastery_longDesc">This character gains +1 on attack and damage rolls when casting an offensive spell from their sorcerer elemental spell list.</string>
	<string name="elemental_mastery_shortDesc">+1 attack/damage on sorc. spells</string>
	<string name="elemental_mastery_page">161</string>

	<string name="empower_name">Empower</string>
	<string name="empower_longDesc">During this character\'s turn, while B2B with a non-incapacitated friendly character, this character can spend 1 feat point to cause the friendly character to regain d3+1 vitality points.</string>
	<string name="empower_shortDesc">Feat: B2B ally gets d3+1 vitality</string>
	<string name="empower_page">161</string>

	<string name="expert_rider_name">Expert Rider</string>
	<string name="expert_rider_longDesc">The character can reroll failed Riding rolls.  Each roll can only be rerolled once due to Expert Rider.  Additionally, this character and their mount cannot be knocked down while the character is mounted and the mount is not knocked out.</string>
	<string name="expert_rider_shortDesc">Reroll Riding, no mounted knockdown</string>
	<string name="expert_rider_page">161</string>

	<string name="fast_cook_name">Fast Cook</string>
	<string name="fast_cook_longDesc">The character can create alchemical items in half the normal time.</string>
	<string name="fast_cook_shortDesc">Create Alchemy in 1/2 time</string>
	<string name="fast_cook_page">161</string>

	<string name="fast_draw_name">Fast Draw</string>
	<string name="fast_draw_longDesc">A character with this skill gains +2 on initiative rolls.  They also gain an additional quick action during the first turn of combat each encounter that can only be used to draw a weapon.</string>
	<string name="fast_draw_shortDesc">+2 Init., free weapon draw</string>
	<string name="fast_draw_page">161</string>

	<string name="fast_rearm_name">Fast Rearm</string>
	<string name="fast_rearm_longDesc">The character gains one extra quick action each turn that can only be used to rearm a weapon of the type noted.  A character can have this ability several times, each with a different weapon.</string>
	<string name="fast_rearm_shortDesc">Free quick action to reload</string>
	<string name="fast_rearm_page">161</string>

	<string name="fast_reload_name">Fast Reload</string>
	<string name="fast_reload_longDesc">The character gains one extra quick action each turn that can be used only to reload a ranged weapon.</string>
	<string name="fast_reload_shortDesc">Free quick action to reload</string>
	<string name="fast_reload_page">161</string>

	<string name="fell_call_cacophony_name">Fell Call: Cacophony</string>
	<string name="fell_call_cacophony_longDesc">The character can use this call as a quick action.  For one round, enemies cannot cast spells, use battle plans, or use drives while in this character\'s command range.</string>
	<string name="fell_call_cacophony_shortDesc">Call: no enemy spells/drives/orders</string>
	<string name="fell_call_cacophony_page">161</string>

	<string name="fell_call_call_of_defiance_name">Fell Call: Call of Defiance</string>
	<string name="fell_call_call_of_defiance_longDesc">The character can use this call as a quick action.  For one round, when a friendly Trollkin character makes a Tough roll while in this character\'s command range, the roll succeeds on a 4, 5, or 6.</string>
	<string name="fell_call_call_of_defiance_shortDesc">Call: Trollkin tough on 4/5/6</string>
	<string name="fell_call_call_of_defiance_page">161</string>

	<string name="fell_call_ground_shaker_name">Fell Call: Ground Shaker</string>
	<string name="fell_call_ground_shaker_longDesc">Once per turn, the character can use this call instead of attacking.  The character makes a RNG 10, AOE 5 fell call ranged attack that causes no damage.  Targets hit are knocked down.</string>
	<string name="fell_call_ground_shaker_shortDesc">Call: RNG 10/AOE 5/POW 0/Knockdown</string>
	<string name="fell_call_ground_shaker_page">162</string>

	<string name="fell_call_heroic_ballad_name">Fell Call: Heroic Ballad</string>
	<string name="fell_call_heroic_ballad_longDesc">The character can use this call as a quick action.  For one round, while in the Fell Caller\'s command range, friendly trollkin are fearless and gain +2 to melee attack rolls.</string>
	<string name="fell_call_heroic_ballad_shortDesc">Call: Trollkin +2 MAT</string>
	<string name="fell_call_heroic_ballad_page">162</string>

	<string name="fell_call_reverberation_name">Fell Call: Reverberation</string>
	<string name="fell_call_reverberation_longDesc">The character can use this call as a quick action.  The character makes a RNG SP 6 ranged attack that causes no damage.  The character uses his POI+Fell Calling skill for his attack rolls.  Enemies hit are pushed d3\" directly away from this character.  Move the enemy who was farthest away first.</string>
	<string name="fell_call_reverberation_shortDesc">Call: SP6/d3\" push</string>
	<string name="fell_call_reverberation_page">162</string>

	<string name="fell_call_signal_call_name">Fell Call: Signal Call</string>
	<string name="fell_call_signal_call_longDesc">The character can use this call as a quick action.  The character can unleash a call that can be heard for a number of miles equal to his Fell Caller skill.</string>
	<string name="fell_call_signal_call_shortDesc">Call: Sound for miles</string>
	<string name="fell_call_signal_call_page">162</string>

	<string name="fell_call_sonic_blast_name">Fell Call: Sonic Blast</string>
	<string name="fell_call_sonic_blast_longDesc">Once per turn, the character can use this call instead of attacking.  The character then makes a RNG SP 8 POW 12 ranged attack.  The character uses his POI+Fell Calling skill for his attack rolls.</string>
	<string name="fell_call_sonic_blast_shortDesc">Call: SP 8 POW 12</string>
	<string name="fell_call_sonic_blast_page">162</string>

	<string name="field_alchemist_name">Field Alchemist</string>
	<string name="field_alchemist_longDesc">The character gains an additional quick action each turn that can only be used to create a field alchemy quick effect.</string>
	<string name="field_alchemist_shortDesc">Field alchemy quick action</string>
	<string name="field_alchemist_page">162</string>

	<string name="field_marshal_magical_attack_name">Field Marshall: Magical Attack</string>
	<string name="field_marshal_magical_attack_longDesc">The warcaster can spend a focus point during his turn to use this ability.  For one round, the weapons of characters in their battlegroup become magical weapons while in the warcaster\'s control area.</string>
	<string name="field_marshal_magical_attack_shortDesc">Focus: B.Group magic weapons</string>
	<string name="field_marshal_magical_attack_page">162</string>

	<string name="field_marshal_relentless_charge_name">Field Marshall: Relentless Charge</string>
	<string name="field_marshal_relentless_charge_longDesc">The warcaster can spend a focus point during his turn to use this ability.  For one round, when a character in the warcaster\'s battlegroup begins a charge while in their control area, that character gains Relentless Charge for their turn.  </string>
	<string name="field_marshal_relentless_charge_shortDesc">Focus: B.Group Relentless Charge</string>
	<string name="field_marshal_relentless_charge_page">162</string>

	<string name="field_marshal_shield_guard_name">Field Marshall: Shield Guard</string>
	<string name="field_marshal_shield_guard_longDesc">The warcaster can spend a focus point during their turn to use this ability.  For one round, characters in their battlegroup gain the Shield Guard ability while in the warcaster\'s control area.</string>
	<string name="field_marshal_shield_guard_shortDesc">Focus: B.Group Shield Guard</string>
	<string name="field_marshal_shield_guard_page">162</string>

	<string name="find_cover_name">Find Cover</string>
	<string name="find_cover_longDesc">At the start of combat before initiative is rolled, this character can immediately advance up to 2\" and perform a quick action to take cover or go prone.</string>
	<string name="find_cover_shortDesc">Before Init.: 2\" move, cover</string>
	<string name="find_cover_page">162</string>

	<string name="fire_in_the_hole_name">Fire in the Hole!</string>
	<string name="fire_in_the_hole_longDesc">This character can make a grenade attack at the start of the Action Phase of their turn before moving or making normal attacks.  A character using this ability must use their movement to run or make a full advance.</string>
	<string name="fire_in_the_hole_shortDesc">Grenade attack before turn</string>
	<string name="fire_in_the_hole_page">163</string>

	<string name="fleet_foot_name">Fleet Foot</string>
	<string name="fleet_foot_longDesc">When the character runs, they move at SPDx3</string>
	<string name="fleet_foot_shortDesc">Run at SPDx3</string>
	<string name="fleet_foot_page">163</string>

	<string name="free_style_name">Free Style</string>
	<string name="free_style_longDesc">The character can improvise the ingredients in their alchemical compounds.  This allows the character to attempt to make do without a specific ingredient.  This requires an Alchemy skill roll with a target number equal to 10 plus the gc value of the ingredient.  This ability also reduces the cost of alchemical compounds by 1 gc each (to a minimum of 1 gc).</string>
	<string name="free_style_shortDesc">Improv alchemical formulae</string>
	<string name="free_style_page">163</string>

	<string name="gang_name">Gang</string>
	<string name="gang_longDesc">When making a melee attack that targets an enemy in melee range of another friendly character, this character gains +1 to melee attacks and melee damage rolls.  If the other friendly character also has Gang, the bonuses increase to +2.</string>
	<string name="gang_shortDesc">+1 attack/damage with ally in melee</string>
	<string name="gang_page">163</string>

	<string name="get_away_name">Get Away</string>
	<string name="get_away_longDesc">When the character is missed by an enemy attack at any time other than while advancing, instead of using any other ability, the character can immediately make a full advance.</string>
	<string name="get_away_shortDesc">Make full advance when missed</string>
	<string name="get_away_page">163</string>

	<string name="girded_name">Girded</string>
	<string name="girded_longDesc">While armed with a shield, this character does not suffer blast damage.  Friendly characters B2B with this character do not suffer blast damage either.</string>
	<string name="girded_shortDesc">You and B2B allies immune to blast damage</string>
	<string name="girded_page">163</string>

	<string name="good_breeding_name">Good Breeding</string>
	<string name="good_breeding_longDesc">The character was raised in high society and can reroll failed Etiquette rolls.  Each roll can only be rerolled once as a result of Good Breeding.</string>
	<string name="good_breeding_shortDesc">Reroll Etiquette rolls</string>
	<string name="good_breeding_page">163</string>

	<string name="great_power_name">Great Power</string>
	<string name="great_power_longDesc">This character can upkeep one spell each turn without spending a focus point or gaining a fatigue point.</string>
	<string name="great_power_shortDesc">One free upkeep</string>
	<string name="great_power_page">163</string>

	<string name="grenadier_name">Grenadier</string>
	<string name="grenadier_longDesc">The character gains an additional quick action each turn that can be used only to pull the pin on a grenade.</string>
	<string name="grenadier_shortDesc">Free quick action to pull pin</string>
	<string name="grenadier_page">163</string>

	<string name="gunfighter_name">Gunfighter</string>
	<string name="gunfighter_longDesc">The character does not suffer a -4 penalty on ranged attack rolls with pistols or carbines while engaged.</string>
	<string name="gunfighter_shortDesc">No -4 ranged penalty when engaged</string>
	<string name="gunfighter_page">163</string>

	<string name="head_butt_name">Head-Butt</string>
	<string name="head_butt_longDesc">Instead of making a normal Unarmed Combat attack, this character can spend a feat point to make a head-butt attack.  The character makes an unarmed melee attack roll against his target.  If the attack hits, the target is knocked down and suffers a damage roll with a POW equal to the character\'s current STR.  A character cannot head-butt a target with a larger base.</string>
	<string name="head_butt_shortDesc">Feat: unarmed attack to knockdown</string>
	<string name="head_butt_page">164</string>

	<string name="hit_the_deck_name">Hit the Deck!</string>
	<string name="hit_the_deck_longDesc">The character has developed the uncanny ability to hit the ground the second before being affected by a blast.  While prone, the character does not suffer damage from AOEs unless directly hit.  If the character would take blast damage from an AOE, they go prone but do not suffer damage.</string>
	<string name="hit_the_deck_shortDesc">Immune to blast damage when prone</string>
	<string name="hit_the_deck_page">164</string>

	<string name="hyper_awareness_name">Hyper Awareness</string>
	<string name="hyper_awareness_longDesc">While in this character\'s command range, friendly characters gain Circular Vision.</string>
	<string name="hyper_awareness_shortDesc">Friendlies gain Circular Vision</string>
	<string name="hyper_awareness_page">164</string>

	<string name="immunity_cold_name">Immunity: Cold</string>
	<string name="immunity_cold_longDesc">The character is immune to cold damage.</string>
	<string name="immunity_cold_shortDesc">Immune to cold damage</string>
	<string name="immunity_cold_page">164</string>

	<string name="immunity_corrosion_name">Immunity: Corrosion</string>
	<string name="immunity_corrosion_longDesc">The character is immune to corrosion damage.</string>
	<string name="immunity_corrosion_shortDesc">Immune to corrosion damage</string>
	<string name="immunity_corrosion_page">164</string>

	<string name="immunity_electricity_name">Immunity: Electricity</string>
	<string name="immunity_electricity_longDesc">The character is immune to electrical damage.</string>
	<string name="immunity_electricity_shortDesc">Immune to electrical damage</string>
	<string name="immunity_electricity_page">164</string>

	<string name="immunity_fire_name">Immunity: Fire</string>
	<string name="immunity_fire_longDesc">The character is immune to fire damage.</string>
	<string name="immunity_fire_shortDesc">Immune to fire damage</string>
	<string name="immunity_fire_page">164</string>

	<string name="inscribe_formulae_name">Inscribe Formulae</string>
	<string name="inscribe_formulae_longDesc">The character can inscribe runeplates; see p. 284</string>
	<string name="inscribe_formulae_shortDesc">Can inscribe runeplates</string>
	<string name="inscribe_formulae_page">284</string>

	<string name="iron_sentinel_name">Iron Sentinel</string>
	<string name="iron_sentinel_longDesc">While B2B with one or more steamjacks they command, this character gains +2 ARM and cannot be knocked down.</string>
	<string name="iron_sentinel_shortDesc">B2B with \'jack: +2 ARM, no knockdown</string>
	<string name="iron_sentinel_page">164</string>

	<string name="iron_will_name">Iron Will</string>
	<string name="iron_will_longDesc">The character can reroll failed Willpower rolls.  Each roll can only be rerolled once due to Iron Will.</string>
	<string name="iron_will_shortDesc">Reroll Willpower</string>
	<string name="iron_will_page">164</string>

	<string name="keen_eyed_name">Keen Eyed</string>
	<string name="keen_eyed_longDesc">The character can increase his effective range with a bow or rifle by 2\" and his extreme range by 10\".</string>
	<string name="keen_eyed_shortDesc">+2\" range with bow/rifle</string>
	<string name="keen_eyed_page">164</string>

	<string name="language_name">Language</string>
	<string name="language_longDesc">This ability can be taken multiple times; each time a character takes this ability, they learn how to speak, read, and write a new language.</string>
	<string name="language_shortDesc">Learn new language</string>
	<string name="language_page">164</string>

	<string name="legacy_of_bragg_name">Legacy of Bragg</string>
	<string name="legacy_of_bragg_longDesc">The character gains an additional quick action each turn that can only be used to make fell calls.</string>
	<string name="legacy_of_bragg_shortDesc">Free quick action for fell calls</string>
	<string name="legacy_of_bragg_page">164</string>

	<string name="light_cavalry_name">Light Cavalry</string>
	<string name="light_cavalry_longDesc">If this character is riding a mount not designated as a warhorse, at the end of their turn they can advance up to 5\".</string>
	<string name="light_cavalry_shortDesc">5\" reserve move on light mount</string>
	<string name="light_cavalry_page">164</string>

	<string name="load_bearing_name">Load Bearing</string>
	<string name="load_bearing_longDesc">Reduce the SPD and DEF penalties from the armor the character wears each by 1.</string>
	<string name="load_bearing_shortDesc">Armor SPD and DEF penalties -1</string>
	<string name="load_bearing_page">164</string>

	<string name="mage_killer_name">Mage Killer</string>
	<string name="mage_killer_longDesc">This character gains an additional die on damage rolls against characters that can cast spells.</string>
	<string name="mage_killer_shortDesc">Extra damage die against spellcasters</string>
	<string name="mage_killer_page">164</string>

	<string name="marksman_name">Marksman</string>
	<string name="marksman_longDesc">The character can use quick actions and aim in the same round, as long as they forfeit their movement to gain the aiming bonus.</string>
	<string name="marksman_shortDesc">Can use quick actions and Aim</string>
	<string name="marksman_page">165</string>

	<string name="natural_leader_name">Natural Leader</string>
	<string name="natural_leader_longDesc">A character with this ability increases their command range by 2\".</string>
	<string name="natural_leader_shortDesc">Command range +2\"</string>
	<string name="natural_leader_page">165</string>

	<string name="night_fighter_name">Night Fighter</string>
	<string name="night_fighter_longDesc">When making a ranged or magic attack against a character with Stealth or Prowl, the attack only automatically misses from 8\" away, rather than 5\".</string>
	<string name="night_fighter_shortDesc">Hit Stealth from 8\" away</string>
	<string name="night_fighter_page">165</string>

	<string name="parry_name">Parry</string>
	<string name="parry_longDesc">While armed with a hand weapon, the character cannot be targeted by free strikes.</string>
	<string name="parry_shortDesc">Immune to free strikes</string>
	<string name="parry_page">165</string>

	<string name="pathfinder_name">Pathfinder</string>
	<string name="pathfinder_longDesc">The character can move over rough terrain without penalty.</string>
	<string name="pathfinder_shortDesc">Move freely over rough terrain</string>
	<string name="pathfinder_page">165</string>

	<string name="poison_resistance_name">Poison Resistance</string>
	<string name="poison_resistance_longDesc">The character gains boosted rolls to resist poisons and toxins</string>
	<string name="poison_resistance_shortDesc">Boosted rolls against poison,toxins</string>
	<string name="poison_resistance_page">165</string>

	<string name="port_of_call_name">Port of Call</string>
	<string name="port_of_call_longDesc">A character with Port of Call can always find their way home again.  For each level of Navigation, a character can nominate one location they\'ve visited more than once as a Port of Call.  When travelling to such a destination and using Navigation, treat any results worse than \"Arrive as planned\" as \"Arrive as planned\".</string>
	<string name="port_of_call_shortDesc">Navigate successfully to home Ports</string>
	<string name="port_of_call_page">165</string>

	<string name="precision_strike_name">Precision Strike</string>
	<string name="precision_strike_longDesc">When the character hits with a melee attack, they choose the branch of the target\'s life spiral or the column of the target\'s damage grid that is hit, if applicable.</string>
	<string name="precision_strike_shortDesc">Choose which damage column is hit</string>
	<string name="precision_strike_page">165</string>

	<string name="press_the_attack_name">Press the Attack</string>
	<string name="press_the_attack_longDesc">When this character slams an enemy, immediately after the slam is resolved this character can advance directly toward the slammed enemy up to the distance the slammed enemy was moved and then make a melee attack against that enemy.</string>
	<string name="press_the_attack_shortDesc">On slam, follow and attack</string>
	<string name="press_the_attack_page">165</string>

	<string name="privilege_name">Privilege</string>
	<string name="privilege_longDesc">This character is afforeded the rights of a noble.  They are immune to persecution for petty crimes and can be tried only by a court of peers.  Should they be found guilty of a high crime, they have the right to be executed in a style befitting a noble.  Each kingdom has distinct benefits and obligations for those born of privilege.  With a successful Etiquette skill roll, this character can demand hospitality and request aid from other nobles not at war with their kingdom.  Additionally, the character gains +2 of social skill rolls when dealing with those beneath their station who recognize their status and respect the nobility.</string>
	<string name="privilege_shortDesc">Treated as a noble</string>
	<string name="privilege_page">165</string>

	<string name="prowl_name">Prowl</string>
	<string name="prowl_longDesc">The character gains Stealth while within terrain that provides concealment, the AOE of a spell that gives concealment, or the AOE of a cloud effect.</string>
	<string name="prowl_shortDesc">Gain Stealth when concealed</string>
	<string name="prowl_page">165</string>

	<string name="pursuit_name">Pursuit</string>
	<string name="pursuit_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point during their turn to use Pursuit.  When this ability is used, the character designates one enemy.  For the rest of the encounter, when that enemy moves during their turn, immediately after the enemy ends their movement this character can make a full advance.  A character can use this benefit only once per encounter unless the original subject of this ability is destroyed, at which point the character can spend a feat point to use this benefit on a new enemy.</string>
	<string name="pursuit_shortDesc">Feat: advance when enemy moves</string>
	<string name="pursuit_page">165</string>

	<string name="quick_work_name">Quick Work</string>
	<string name="quick_work_longDesc">When this character kills one or more enemies with a melee attack during their combat action, immediately after that attack is resolved this character can make one ranged attack, if a ranged weapon is held and loaded.</string>
	<string name="quick_work_shortDesc">Free ranged attack after melee kill</string>
	<string name="quick_work_page">166</string>

	<string name="rallying_cry_name">Rallying Cry</string>
	<string name="rallying_cry_longDesc">This character can spend a feat point to use this ability.  For one round, this character\'s command range is doubled and friendly characters in their command range become fearless.</string>
	<string name="rallying_cry_shortDesc">Feat: 2x CMD + Fearless</string>
	<string name="rallying_cry_page">166</string>

	<string name="relentless_charge_name">Relentless Charge</string>
	<string name="relentless_charge_longDesc">This character ignores penalties for rough terrain while charging.</string>
	<string name="relentless_charge_shortDesc">Ignore rough terrain on charge</string>
	<string name="relentless_charge_page">166</string>

	<string name="resourceful_name">Resourceful</string>
	<string name="resourceful_longDesc">This character can upkeep spells on steamjacks they control without spending focus or gaining fatigue points.</string>
	<string name="resourceful_shortDesc">Free \'jack spell upkeep</string>
	<string name="resourceful_page">166</string>

	<string name="retaliatory_strike_name">Retaliatory Strike</string>
	<string name="retaliatory_strike_longDesc">When this character is hit by an enemy\'s melee attack outside of their turn, after the attack is resolved they can spend one feat point to immediately make one normal melee attack against the enemy that hit him.</string>
	<string name="retaliatory_strike_shortDesc">Feat: melee attack when hit</string>
	<string name="retaliatory_strike_page">166</string>

	<string name="return_fire_ability_name">Return Fire</string>
	<string name="return_fire_ability_longDesc">Once per round when this character is missed by an enemy\'s ranged attack, immediately after the attack is resolved they can make one normal attack against the attacking enemy if a ranged weapon is held and loaded.</string>
	<string name="return_fire_ability_shortDesc">Free ranged attack when missed</string>
	<string name="return_fire_ability_page">166</string>

	<string name="ride_by_attack_name">Ride-By Attack</string>
	<string name="ride_by_attack_longDesc">While mounted, this character can combine their movement and action during their turn to make a Ride-By Attack.  The character declares a Ride-By Attack at the start of their Activation Phase.  They make a full advance and can halt movement at any point to make attacks, and resume movement afterwards.</string>
	<string name="ride_by_attack_shortDesc">Mounted: attack during move</string>
	<string name="ride_by_attack_page">166</string>

	<string name="riposte_name">Riposte</string>
	<string name="riposte_longDesc">Once per round when this character is missed by an enemy\'s melee attack, immediately after the attack is resolved they can make one normal attack against the attacking character.  To make a ranged attack, the character must be holding a loaded ranged weapon.</string>
	<string name="riposte_shortDesc">Once/round, free attack when missed</string>
	<string name="riposte_page">166</string>

	<string name="rock_solid_name">Rock Solid</string>
	<string name="rock_solid_longDesc">This character and characters B2B with them cannot be knocked down.  This ability is lost when the character is mounted.</string>
	<string name="rock_solid_shortDesc">You+B2B immune to knockdown</string>
	<string name="rock_solid_page">166</string>

	<string name="roll_with_it_name">Roll With It</string>
	<string name="roll_with_it_longDesc">When the character would ordinarily be knocked down, they go prone instead.  This ability is lost when the character is mounted.</string>
	<string name="roll_with_it_shortDesc">Prone instead of knockdown</string>
	<string name="roll_with_it_page">166</string>

	<string name="saddle_shot_name">Saddle Shot</string>
	<string name="saddle_shot_longDesc">This character does not suffer the firing-from-horseback penalty when making ranged attacks while mounted.</string>
	<string name="saddle_shot_shortDesc">No firing-from-horseback penalty</string>
	<string name="saddle_shot_page">166</string>

	<string name="scrounge_name">Scrounge</string>
	<string name="scrounge_longDesc">The character is adept at finding hard-to-acquire or expensive replacement parts to repair steamjacks.  Given a day to find the parts in a town or industrialized settlement, the character can find any part needed (or something close enough he can bodge it together).  The character can purchase steamjack parts, weapons, and gear for half the normal price.</string>
	<string name="scrounge_shortDesc">Always find \'jack parts, 1/2 price</string>
	<string name="scrounge_page">167</string>

	<string name="sentry_name">Sentry</string>
	<string name="sentry_longDesc">Once per round, when an enemy is placed in or moves into the line of sight of this character, this character can immediately make one attack, targeting that enemy.</string>
	<string name="sentry_shortDesc">Ask your GM</string>
	<string name="sentry_page">167</string>

	<string name="set_defense_name">Set Defense</string>
	<string name="set_defense_longDesc">While this character is armed with a weapon that has reach, an enemy in this character\'s front arc suffers -2 on charge, slam, power attack, and impact attack rolls against them.</string>
	<string name="set_defense_shortDesc">Reach: -2 on enemy power attack rolls</string>
	<string name="set_defense_page">167</string>

	<string name="shadow_magic_name">Shadow Magic</string>
	<string name="shadow_magic_longDesc">When this character casts a spell, no spell runes appear and magically sensitive characters cannot sense the character\'s magic.  A focuser with this ability cannot be detected by another focuser with the Magic Sensitivity archetype benefit.</string>
	<string name="shadow_magic_shortDesc">Magic ability undetectable</string>
	<string name="shadow_magic_page">167</string>

	<string name="shield_guard_name">Shield Guard</string>
	<string name="shield_guard_longDesc">Once per turn, when a friendly character is directly hit by an attack while within 2\" of this character, this character can choose to be directly hit instead.  This character cannot use this ability while incorporeal, knocked down, prone, or stationary.</string>
	<string name="shield_guard_shortDesc">Take hit for friend</string>
	<string name="shield_guard_page">167</string>

	<string name="shield_slam_name">Shield Slam</string>
	<string name="shield_slam_longDesc">When this character charges while armed with a shield, instead of making a charge attack, they can spend a feat point to slam their targets making an attack roll with their shield.  A character who slams another character with a larger base suffers a -2 to this attack roll.  The POW of the slam damage roll is equal to the STR of the attacking character plus the POW of the shield.  The POW of collateral damage is equal to the STR of the attacking character.</string>
	<string name="shield_slam_shortDesc">Feat: slam attack with shield</string>
	<string name="shield_slam_page">167</string>

	<string name="signal_language_name">Signal Language</string>
	<string name="signal_language_longDesc">The character can spend time developing a coded signal language for use with the part using the same rules as creatiang a code.  The language can convey simple messages or commands and has a Cryptography target number based on the target number used during the code\'s creation.  The signal language can be taught to any character that has Intellect 3 or greater.</string>
	<string name="signal_language_shortDesc">Can make signal language</string>
	<string name="signal_language_page">167</string>

	<string name="sniper_name">Sniper</string>
	<string name="sniper_longDesc">When this character forfeits their movement to aim during their turn, the character\'s first ranged attack that turn gains boosted damage.</string>
	<string name="sniper_shortDesc">Aim: first attack boosted damage</string>
	<string name="sniper_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>

	<string name="specialization_name">Specialization</string>
	<string name="specialization_longDesc">The character does not suffer the weapon\'s attack roll penalties when attacking with a weapon of the type chosen.  A character can have this ability several times, each time choosing a different weapon.</string>
	<string name="specialization_shortDesc">No attack penalty from weapon</string>
	<string name="specialization_page">167</string>

	<string name="steady_name">Steady</string>
	<string name="steady_longDesc">This character cannot be knocked down.  This ability does not apply while mounted.</string>
	<string name="steady_shortDesc">Immune to knockdown</string>
	<string name="steady_page">167</string>

	<string name="steamo_name">Steamo</string>
	<string name="steamo_longDesc">The character can reroll failed Mechanikal Engineering rolls to repair or dismantle steamjacks.  Each roll can be rerolled only once as a result of Steamo.</string>
	<string name="steamo_shortDesc">Reroll Mech. Engineering rolls</string>
	<string name="steamo_page">167</string>

	<string name="sucker_name">Sucker!</string>
	<string name="sucker_longDesc">If this character is directly hit by an enemy ranged attack, they can choose a friendly, living, non-incorporeal character within 2\" to be hit instead.  That character is automatically hit and suffers all damage and effects.</string>
	<string name="sucker_shortDesc">Pass hits to friends</string>
	<string name="sucker_page">167</string>

	<string name="swift_hunter_name">Swift Hunter</string>
	<string name="swift_hunter_longDesc">When this character incapacitates an enemy by using a normal ranged attack, immediately after the attack is resolved they can advance up to 2\".</string>
	<string name="swift_hunter_shortDesc">Ranged kill: move 2\"</string>
	<string name="swift_hunter_page">167</string>

	<string name="swift_rider_name">Swfit Rider</string>
	<string name="swift_rider_longDesc">While riding a mount, the character can move over rough terrian without penalty.</string>
	<string name="swift_rider_shortDesc">Mounted: no rough terrain penalty</string>
	<string name="swift_rider_page">167</string>

	<string name="take_down_name">Take Down</string>
	<string name="take_down_longDesc">This character can use this ability anytime they incapacitate another character with an attack if the incapacitated character is in this character\'s melee range.  The incapacitated character regains 1 vitality point and is no longer incapacitated but is considered to be manacled, tied up, unconscious, or otherwise out of action for the rest of the encounter.  Once the combat portion of the encounter has ended, the subject of the take down is at the mercy of the victors to be questioned or worse.</string>
	<string name="take_down_shortDesc">Keep enemies alive after kill</string>
	<string name="take_down_page">167</string>

	<string name="targeteer_name">Targeteer</string>
	<string name="targeteer_longDesc">When the character hits with a ranged attack, they choose the branch of the target\'s life spiral or the column of the target\'s damage grid that is hit, if applicable.</string>
	<string name="targeteer_shortDesc">Ranged: choose spiral to damage</string>
	<string name="targeteer_page">168</string>

	<string name="team_leader_name">Team Leader</string>
	<string name="team_leader_longDesc">When this character gains a feat point, instead of keeping it they can give it to another character currently in their command range.</string>
	<string name="team_leader_shortDesc">Can give feats to friends</string>
	<string name="team_leader_page">168</string>

	<string name="traceless_path_name">Traceless Path</string>
	<string name="traceless_path_longDesc">The character knows how to conceal their trail when moving over land.  Though they can easily move at only half their usual rate of speed while using this ability, either on foot or horseback, anyone attempting to follow their trail has +3 added to the skill roll target number.</string>
	<string name="traceless_path_shortDesc">No trail at 1/2 speed</string>
	<string name="traceless_path_page">168</string>

	<string name="truth_reader_name">Truth Reader</string>
	<string name="truth_reader_longDesc">The character automatically knows when someone is lying to them.  Keep in mind that knowing someone is lying is different than discerning the truth.</string>
	<string name="truth_reader_shortDesc">Automatically detect lies</string>
	<string name="truth_reader_page">168</string>

	<string name="tune_up_name">Tune Up</string>
	<string name="tune_up_longDesc">While B2B with a steamjack they control, this character can spend a quick action to use this ability.  During its turn this round, the steamjack gains either boosted attack or damage rolls.</string>
	<string name="tune_up_shortDesc">Quick action: B2B \'jack gets boosted rolls</string>
	<string name="tune_up_page">168</string>

	<string name="two_weapon_fighting_name">Two-Weapon Fighting</string>
	<string name="two_weapon_fighting_longDesc">While fighting with a one-handed weapon or pistol in each hand, the character gains an additional attack for the second weapon.  They suffer -2 on attack rolls with the second weapon while doing so.</string>
	<string name="two_weapon_fighting_shortDesc">Extra attack with off-hand</string>
	<string name="two_weapon_fighting_page">168</string>

	<string name="university_education_name">University Education</string>
	<string name="university_education_longDesc">The character can reroll failed Lore and Research skill rolls.  Each roll can be rerolled only once as a result of University Education.</string>
	<string name="university_education_shortDesc">Reroll Lore/Research rolls</string>
	<string name="university_education_page">168</string>

	<string name="waylay_name">Waylay</string>
	<string name="waylay_longDesc">When an attack made by this character has the chance to knock out a target, increase the target number for the Willpower roll to resist the knockout by 2</string>
	<string name="waylay_shortDesc">Knockouts need +2 Willpower</string>
	<string name="waylay_page">168</string>
	
	<!--Archetype abilities-->
		
		<!--GIFTED-->
	<string name="additional_study_name">Additional Study</string>
	<string name="additional_study_longDesc">This character delves further into the mysteries of the arcane and is rewarded with a spell from one of their career spell lists.  The benefit can be taken multiple times, but a character cannot exceed their known spell limit.</string>
	<string name="additional_study_shortDesc">Learn additional spell</string>
	<string name="additional_study_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="combat_caster_name">Combat Caster</string>
	<string name="combat_caster_longDesc">When this character makes a magic attack roll, they gain an additional die.  Discard the lowest die of each roll.</string>
	<string name="combat_caster_shortDesc">+1 die on magic attacks, discard lowest</string>
	<string name="combat_caster_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="fast_caster_name">Fast Caster</string>
	<string name="fast_caster_longDesc">The character gains one extra quick action each activation that can be used only to cast a spell.</string>
	<string name="fast_caster_shortDesc">Free quick action to cast spells</string>
	<string name="fast_caster_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="feat_dominator_name">Feat: Dominator</string>
	<string name="feat_dominator_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point during their turn to double their control area for one round.</string>
	<string name="feat_dominator_shortDesc">Feat: 2x control range</string>
	<string name="feat_dominator_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="feat_powerful_caster_name">Feat: Powerful Caster</string>
	<string name="feat_powerful_caster_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point when they cast a spell to increase the RNG of the spell by 2\".  Spells with a range of CTRL or SP are not affected.</string>
	<string name="feat_powerful_caster_shortDesc">Feat: spell RNG +2\"</string>
	<string name="feat_powerful_caster_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="feat_quick_cast_name">Feat: Quick Cast</string>
	<string name="feat_quick_cast_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point to immediately cast one upkeep spell at the start of combat.  When casting a spell as a result of this benefit, the character is not required to pay the COST of the spell.</string>
	<string name="feat_quick_cast_shortDesc">Feat: gain upkeep before battle</string>
	<string name="feat_quick_cast_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="feat_strength_of_will_name">Feat: Strength of Will</string>
	<string name="feat_strength_of_will_longDesc">After failing a fatigue roll, the character can spend 1 feat point to instead automatically succeed on the roll.  This benefit can only be taken by Will Weavers.</string>
	<string name="feat_strength_of_will_shortDesc">Feat: pass a failed fatigue roll</string>
	<string name="feat_strength_of_will_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="magic_sensitivity_name">Magic Sensitivity</string>
	<string name="magic_sensitivity_longDesc">The character can automatically sense when another character casts a spell within fifty feet for each point of their ARC stat.  Such characters can tune out this detection as background noise but are aware of particularly powerful magic.  Additionally, a character with the focuser tradition can sense other focusers within their detection range.</string>
	<string name="magic_sensitivity_shortDesc">Detect magic users</string>
	<string name="magic_sensitivity_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="rune_reader_name">Rune Reader</string>
	<string name="rune_reader_longDesc">The character can identify any spell cast in their line of sight by reading the accompanying spell runes.  They can also learn the spell list the spell came from, and the tradition of the caster.</string>
	<string name="rune_reader_shortDesc">Identify cast magic</string>
	<string name="rune_reader_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="warding_circle_name">Warding Circle</string>
	<string name="warding_circle_longDesc">The character can spend 15 minutes to create a circle of warding runes around a small room or campsite.  The names of the character they intend to keep safe within the circle are incorporated into the runes.  When any other character enters the circle, all named characters are alerted.  While in the circle, non-named characters lose incorporeal, and non-named undead and infernal characters suffer -2 on attack rolls.</string>
	<string name="warding_circle_shortDesc">Create warding circle</string>
	<string name="warding_circle_page">115</string>
	
		<!--INTELLECTUAL-->
	<string name="battlefield_coordination_name">Battlefield Coordination</string>
	<string name="battlefield_coordination_longDesc">While in this character\'s command range, friendly characters do not suffer the firing into melee penalty and do not have a chance to hit friendly characters when they miss with attacks while firing into melee.</string>
	<string name="battlefield_coordination_shortDesc">Prevent firing-into-melee penalty</string>
	<string name="battlefield_coordination_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="feat_flawless_timing_name">Feat: Flawless Timing</string>
	<string name="feat_flawless_timing_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point to use this benefit during their turn.  When they use Flawless Timing, the character names an enemy.  The next time that enemy directly hits them with an attack that encounter, the attack misses instead.</string>
	<string name="feat_flawless_timing_shortDesc">Feat: force enemy to miss</string>
	<string name="feat_flawless_timing_page">115</string>
	
	<string name="feat_prescient_name">Feat: Prescient</string>
	<string name="feat_prescient_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point to win initiative automatically.  If two or more characters use this ability, they make initiative rolls to determine which of them goes first.</string>
	<string name="feat_prescient_shortDesc">Feat: Win initiative</string>
	<string name="feat_prescient_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_perfect_plot_name">Feat: Perfect Plot</string>
	<string name="feat_perfect_plot_longDesc">The character is a flawless planner and allows nothing to escape their attention.  Assuming they are able to oversee all aspects of the plan, scout out the related sites, and do research in great detail, they are sure to succeed.  A character must spend 1 feat point to use this ability.  A character following this character\'s plans gains an additional die on non-combat related rolls during the day in which the plan was enacted.</string>
	<string name="feat_perfect_plot_shortDesc">Feat: plan, get boosted skill rolls</string>
	<string name="feat_perfect_plot_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_plan_of_action_name">Feat: Plan of Action</string>
	<string name="feat_plan_of_action_longDesc">At the start of combat, the character can spend 1 feat point to use this benefit.  During that combat, all characters who follow the plan gain +2 to their initiative rolls and +2 to their attack rolls during the first round of combat.</string>
	<string name="feat_plan_of_action_shortDesc">Feat: +2 Init., +2 attack firt round</string>
	<string name="feat_plan_of_action_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_quick_thinking_name">Feat: Quick Thinking</string>
	<string name="feat_quick_thinking_longDesc">Once per round, the character can spend 1 feat point to make one attack or quick action at the start of another character\'s turn.</string>
	<string name="feat_quick_thinking_shortDesc">Feat: Attack or quick action on other\'s turn</string>
	<string name="feat_quick_thinking_page">116!</string>
	
	<string name="feat_unconventional_warfare_name">Feat: Unconventional Warfare</string>
	<string name="feat_unconventional_warfare_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point to assess the situation and gain a benefit in combat.  The player must explain to the GM how they are turning the environment against their enemy.  The GM then determines the likely effect of the character\'s action or attack.  Outcomes include a boosted damage roll, knockdown, push, slam, or a fall from a height.</string>
	<string name="feat_unconventional_warfare_shortDesc">Feat: use environment in battle</string>
	<string name="feat_unconventional_warfare_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="genius_name">Genius</string>
	<string name="genius_longDesc">The character\'s INT rolls are boosted.</string>
	<string name="genius_shortDesc">Boosted INT rolls</string>
	<string name="genius_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="hyper_perception_name">Hyper Perception</string>
	<string name="hyper_perception_longDesc">The character\'s PER rolls are boosted.</string>
	<string name="hyper_perception_shortDesc">Boosted PER rolls</string>
	<string name="hyper_perception_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="photographic_memory_name">Photographic Memory</string>
	<string name="photographic_memory_longDesc">The character can recall every event in perfect detail.  During play they can call upon their memory to ask the GM questions pertaining to anything they have seen or experienced.</string>
	<string name="photographic_memory_shortDesc">Ask GM for old details</string>
	<string name="photographic_memory_page">116</string>
	
		<!--MIGHTY-->
	<string name="beat_back_name">Beat Back</string>
	<string name="beat_back_longDesc">When this character hits a target with a melee attack, they can immediately push their target 1\" directly away.  After the target is pushed, this character can advance up to 1\".</string>
	<string name="beat_back_shortDesc">1\" push and move up</string>
	<string name="beat_back_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_back_swing_name">Feat: Back Swing</string>
	<string name="feat_back_swing_longDesc">Once per turn, this character can spend 1 feat point to gain one additional melee attack.</string>
	<string name="feat_back_swing_shortDesc">Feat: extra melee attack</string>
	<string name="feat_back_swing_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_bounding_leap_name">Feat: Bounding Leap</string>
	<string name="feat_bounding_leap_longDesc">Once per turn, if the character does not run or charge, they can spend 1 feat point to place themself anywhere within 5\" of their current location.</string>
	<string name="feat_bounding_leap_shortDesc">Feat: 5\" place</string>
	<string name="feat_bounding_leap_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_counter_charge_name">Feat: Counter Charge</string>
	<string name="feat_counter_charge_longDesc">When an enemy advances and ends its movement within 6\" of this character and in their line of sight, this character can immeidately spend 1 feat point to charge the enemy.  The character cannot make a counter charge while engaged.</string>
	<string name="feat_counter_charge_shortDesc">Feat: charge enemy stopping within 6\"</string>
	<string name="feat_counter_charge_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_invulnerable_name">Feat: Invulnerable</string>
	<string name="feat_invulnerable_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point during their turn to gain +3 ARM for one round.</string>
	<string name="feat_invulnerable_shortDesc">+3 ARM for one round</string>
	<string name="feat_invulnerable_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_revitalize_name">Feat: Revitalize</string>
	<string name="feat_revitalize_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point during their turn to immediately regain a number of vitality points equal to their PHY stat.  An incapacitated character cannot use Revitalize.</string>
	<string name="feat_revitalize_shortDesc">Feat: recover PHY points of vitality</string>
	<string name="feat_revitalize_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_shield_breaker_name">Feat: Shield Breaker</string>
	<string name="feat_shield_breaker_longDesc">When this character hits with a melee attack against a target that has a shield, the character can spend 1 feat point to completely destory the other character\'s shield after the damage has been dealt.</string>
	<string name="feat_shield_breaker_shortDesc">Feat: destroy enemy shield</string>
	<string name="feat_shield_breaker_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="feat_vendetta_name">Feat: Vendetta</string>
	<string name="feat_vendetta_longDesc">The character can spend 1 feat point during their turn to use this benefit.  When used, the character names one enemy.  For the rest of the encounter, this character gains boosted attack rolls against that enemy.  A character can use this benefit only once per encounter unless the original subject of the vendetta is destroyed, at which point the character can spend a feat point to use this benefit again.</string>
	<string name="feat_vendetta_shortDesc">Feat: boost attacks against chosen enemy</string>
	<string name="feat_vendetta_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="righteous_anger_name">Righteous Anger</string>
	<string name="righteous_anger_longDesc">When one or more friendly characters are damaged by an enemy attack while in this character\'s command range, this character gains +2 STR and ARM for one round.</string>
	<string name="righteous_anger_shortDesc">+2 STR, ARM when friend hurt</string>
	<string name="righteous_anger_page">116</string>
	
	<string name="tough_name">Tough</string>
	<string name="tough_longDesc">When this character is disabled, roll a d6.  On a 5 or 6, the character heals 1 vitality point, is no longer disabled, and is knocked down.</string>
	<string name="tough_shortDesc">Recover on 5/6 when disabled</string>
	<string name="tough_page">116</string>
	
		<!--SKILLED-->
	<string name="ambidextrous_name">Ambidextrous</string>
	<string name="ambidextrous_longDesc">The character does not suffer the attack roll penalty for the second weapon when using the Two-Weapon Fighting ability.</string>
	<string name="ambidextrous_shortDesc">No penalty when Two-Weapon Fighting</string>
	<string name="ambidextrous_page">117</string>
	
	<string name="cagey_name">Cagey</string>
	<string name="cagey_longDesc">When this character is knocked down, they can immediately move up to 2\" and cannot be targeted by free strikes.  While knocked down, this character is not automatically hit by melee attacks and their DEF is not reduced.  The character can stand up during their turn without forfeiting their movement or action.  This benefit does not apply while mounted.</string>
	<string name="cagey_shortDesc">No penalties from knockdown</string>
	<string name="cagey_page">117</string>
	
	<string name="deft_name">Deft</string>
	<string name="deft_longDesc">This character gains boosted AGL rolls</string>
	<string name="deft_shortDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="deft_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	
	<string name="feat_defensive_strike_name">Hello World, MainActivity</string>
	<string name="feat_defensive_strike_longDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_defensive_strike_shortDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_defensive_strike_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	
	<string name="feat_disarm_name">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_disarm_longDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_disarm_shortDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_disarm_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	
	<string name="feat_swashbuckler_name">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_swashbuckler_longDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_swashbuckler_shortDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_swashbuckler_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	
	<string name="feat_untouchable_name">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_untouchable_longDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_untouchable_shortDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="feat_untouchable_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	
	<string name="preternatural_awareness_name">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="preternatural_awareness_longDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="preternatural_awareness_shortDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="preternatural_awareness_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	
	<string name="sidestep_name">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="sidestep_longDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="sidestep_shortDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="sidestep_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	
	<string name="virtuoso_name">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="virtuoso_longDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="virtuoso_shortDesc">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="virtuoso_page">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	
</resources>
